Finding Aid for Museum of Art (University of Michigan) records, 1946-2003
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Exhibition Files, 1946-2003
  - 1954-1955
    - "Recent Gifts to the Museum,", July 26-September 7, 1954 (Box 3)
    - "Contemporary Paintings and Drawings-Museum Collections,", September 10-October 5, 1954 (Box 3)
    - "Olivetti: Design in Industry,", September 19-October 5, 1954 (Box 3)
    - "Post-War European Photography,", September 19-October 7, 1954 (Box 3)
    - "The Classical Motif,", October 8-29, 1954 (Box 3)
    - "French Painting at Mid-Century,", October 10-31, 1954 (Box 3)
    - "Styles in Chinese Painting,", November 3-23, 1954 (Box 3)
    - "Color Print Series-Museum Collections,", November 3-23, 1954 (Box 3)
      (includes Chagall, Pascin, Mérida)
    - "Plastic and Graphic Expressions by Modern Sculptors,", November 7-30, 1954 (Box 3)
    - "French Textiles, 1685-1800,", November 28, 1954-January 2, 1955 (Box 3)
    - "Whistler Prints,", November 28, 1954-January 2, 1955 (Box 3)
    - "Michigan Printmakers Society,", January 3-23, 1955 (Box 3)
    - "Contemporary Folk Art of Japan,", January 6-25, 1955 (Box 3)
    - "Contemporary Paintings and Drawings-Museum Collections,", January 6-February 9, 1955 (Box 3)
    - "Art Print Loan Collection,", January 13-February 4, 1955 (Box 3)
    - "Fantastic Landscapes,", February 13-March 6, 1955 (Box 3)
    - "Michigan Water Color Society,", February 13-March 6, 1955 (Box 3)
    - "Schulke in Mexico" (Harry Schulke), February 13-March 6, 1955 (Box 3)
    - "Religious Prints and Drawings-Museum Collections,", February 21-March 6, 1955 (Box 3)
    - "Contemporary American Drawings,", March 13-April 3, 1955 (Box 3)
    - "Lithographs of Georges Braque,", March 13-April 3, 1955 (Box 3)
    - "Contemporary Paintings and French Drawings-Museum Collections,", April 6-30, 1955 (Box 3)
    - "Bruguiere Photographs,", April 10-May 1, 1955 (Box 3)
      (George Eastman House)
    - "A Student Collects,", April 10-May 1, 1955 (Box 3)
    - "Hispanic Festival,", April 18-22, 1955 (Box 3)
    - "Student Exhibition-College of Architecture and Design,", May 6-26, 1955 (Box 3)
      (includes installation photograph)
    - "Museum Collections (Old Master Prints; American Drawings' Contemporary Paintings and French Drawings),", May 28-June 12, 1955 (Box 3)
  - 1955-1956
    - Schedule (Box 3)
    - "Michigan Art Through Fifty Years,", June 26-July 31, 1955 (Box 3)
    - "Old Master Prints and Contemporary Paintings-Museum Collections,", June 26-July 31, 1955 (Box 3)
    - "Life in America; American Drawings; Contemporary Paintings and French Drawings-Museum Collections," August 1-12, September 6-27, 1955 (Box 3)
    - "Prints of the High Renaissance,", October 2-23, 1955 (Box 3)
    - "Graphic Works by Robert Adams,", October 2-23, 1955 (Box 3)
      (Department of Art, Douglass College, Rutgers University)
    - "University of Washington Faculty Show,", October 5-25, 1955 (Box 3)
    - "20th Century Painting and Sculpture from the Winston Collection,", October 30-November 27, 1955 (Box 3)
    - "Major Work in Minor Scale: Italian Sculptors and Painters,", November 1-22, 1955 (Box 3)
    - "British Art in the Museum Collection,", December 1-22, 1955 (Box 3)
    - "Edward Littman Collection of Expressionist Prints,", December 6-27, 1955 (Box 3)
    - "Contemporary Paintings and Drawings (and Sculpture and Ceramics)-Museum Collections,", November 23-December 21, 1955 (Box 3)
    - "The Versatile Medium,", December 28, 1955-January 18, 1956 (Box 3)
    - "Modern Prints from the Museum Collection,", December 29, 1955-February 14, 1956 (Box 3)
    - "Swedish Children's Paintings,", January 3-26, 1956 (Box 3)
    - "Prints: Modern Italians, Picasso, Rouault-Museum Collections,", January 19-February 8, 1956 (Box 3)
    - "Drawings (American, French and Mixed)-Museum Collections,", January 23-February 14, 1956 (Box 3)
    - "Immaculate Heart College Student Exhibition,", February 5-26, 1956 (Box 3)
    - "Etchings by Matisse,", February 11-March 3, 1956 (Box 3)
      (Museum of Modern Art and UMMA)
    - "Contemporary Finnish Architecture,", February 19-March 11, 1956 (Box 3)
      (Smithsonian Institution: National Collection of Fine Arts, and Association of Finnish Architects & Finnish-American Society)
    - "Margaret Watson Parker Collection,", February 29-April 29, 1956 (Box 3)
    - "Drawings from the Oberlin Collection,", March 11-April 1, 1956 (Box 3)
    - "Smith College Collects,", April 8-29, 1956 (Box 3)
    - "Hispanic Festival,", April 11-13, 1956 (Box 3)
      (Romance Language Department)
    - "Woodcuts by Kiyoshi Saito,", April 17-23, 1956 (Box 3)
    - "Student Exhibition-College of Architecture and Design,", May 6-27, 1956 (Box 3)
    - "Museum Collections,", June 1-30, 1956 (Box 3)
  - 1956-1957
    - Schedule (Box 3)
    - "Contemporary Prints; Contemporary Drawings-Museum Collections,", July 1-September 26, 1956 (Box 3)
    - "Eight New York Painters,", July 1-31, 1956 (Box 3)
      (part of the "Patterns of American Culture: Contributions of the Negro" summer session)
      (includes correspondence with the artists)
    - "Zen '49 Group,", August 22-September 26, 1956 (Box 3)
      (Ohio Wesleyan University, Departments of Fine Arts and German)
    - "Alexander Calder-Mobiles and Stabiles,", September 16-October 14, 1956 (Box 3)
      (Perl Galleries and Wisconsin Union of the University of Wisconsin)
    - "'Japan' by Werner Bischoff,", September 30-October 18, 1956 (Box 3)
    - "Semi-Centennial Celebration: College of Architecture and Design" (Alumni Exhibition), October 24-November 4, 1956 (Box 3)
    - "Michigan Printmakers,", November 7-27, 1956 (Box 3)
    - "Dutch and German Prints, 15th, 16th and 17th Centuries-Museum Collections,", November 6-29, 1956 (Box 3)
    - "Textiles and Stencils from Japan" (Museum of Modern Art), November 7-30, 1956 (Box 3)
    - "Figures and Faces,", November 24-December 16, 1956 (Box 3)
    - "Vollard Prints in the Museum Collection,", December 1-31, 1956 (Box 3)
    - Contemporary Paintings and Drawings to travel to Nebraska, December 3-31, 1956 (Box 3)
    - "Chagall's Lithographs for Arabian Nights-Museum Collection,", December 19, 1956-February 18, 1957 (Box 3)
    - "American and European Serigraphs,", December 19, 1956-January 27, 1957 (Box 3)
      (Meltzer Gallery)
    - "25 Years of A.H. Mauer,", January 4-February 6, 1957 (Box 3)
    - "Contemporary Sculpture, Drawings and Prints-Museum Collections,", January 4-February 6, 1957 (Box 3)
    - "Paintings from the University of Nebraska Art Galleries,", February 10-March 10, 1957 (Box 3)
    - "Old Master Drawings-Museum Collections,", February 1-28, 1957 (Box 3)
    - "Venetian Villas,", February 24-March 26, 1957 (Box 3)
    - "Calvin Albert-Sculpture and Drawings,", March 3-24, 1957 (Box 3)
      (Grace Borgenicht Gallery Inc.)
    - "16th-20th Century Religious Prints,", March 14-April 7, 1957 (Box 3)
    - "California Painters,", March 31-May 5, 1957 (Box 3)
    - "Contemporary Color Prints-Museum Collections,", March 28-June 15, 1957 (Box 3)
    - "Young Collectors' Print Exhibition,", April 11-May 2, 1957 (Box 3)
      (Roten Art Frame Studio)
    - "Lyrical and Accurate,", May 1-29, 1957 (Box 3)
      (George Eastman House of Photography)
    - "Contemporary Paintings-Museum Collections,", May 4-June 15, 1957 (Box 3)
    - "50 Modern Drawings,", May 9-June 15, 1957 (Box 3)
      (American Federation of Arts traveling exhibition)
    - "Contemporary Sculpture-Museum Collections,", June 1-15, 1957 (Box 3)
    - "Photographs by Margaret Bourke-White,", June 10-15, 1957 (Box 3)
      (Life Magazine)
  - 1957-1958
    - Schedule (Box 4)
    - Undergraduate Library exhibitions, 1957-1958 (Box 4)
    - Summer exhibitions, general material, July, August 1957 (Box 4)
    - "Japan Society Exhibitions" (Costumes & Fabrics, Modern Prints, Dolls, Stamps), Summer 1957 (Box 4)
      (Japan Society, Inc. and Society for International Cultural Relations of Tokyo)
    - "Architecture of Japan,", July 8-August 8, 1957 (Box 4)
    - "Graphic Work of Ben Shahn,", October 11-31, 1957 (Box 4)
      (American Institute of Graphic Arts)
    - "Contemporary Color Lithographs" (from Cincinnati Art Museum's Fourth International Biennial), November 5-20, 1957 (Box 4)
    - Print Exhibition, November-December 1957 (Box 4)
    - "Craftsmanship in a Changing World" (Museum of Contemporary Crafts, New York City), November 8-23, 1957 (Box 4)
    - "Prints by Matisse,", November 26-December 17, 1957 (Box 4)
    - "AFA Preview: Younger Europeans,", January 15-28, 1958 (Box 4)
    - "Fifty Books of the Year,", February 2-23, 1958 (Box 4)
    - "Modern Church Architecture,", February 11-March 4, 1958 (Box 4)
    - "Painting Techniques,", March 1958 (Box 4)
      (National Gallery of Art)
    - "Good Design in Switzerland" (Swiss Werkbund), March 9-30, 1958 (Box 4)
    - "Jack Garbutt Show,", March 10-April 6, 1958 (Box 4)
    - "This Is the American Earth,", March 16-April 6, 1958 (Box 4)
      (NOT SHOWN)
    - "The American Cartoon,", April 12-May 3, 1958 (Box 4)
    - "Mexican Art: Pre-Columbian to Modern Times,", April 17-June 15, 1958
      - Galeria Proteo Arte Contemporaneo, Mexico City, Mexico (Box 4)
      - Ines Amor, Galleria de Arte Mexicana (Box 4)
      - Publicity (Box 4)
      - Pre-Columbian (Box 4)
      - Colonial (Box 4)
      - Contemporary (Box 4)
      - Architecture (Box 4)
      - Museum of Modern Art (Box 4)
      - Catalogue text (Box 4)
      - Progress reports to circulators (Box 4)
      - Lenders-United States (Box 4)
      - Symposium
        - Project report (Box 4)
        - News releases (Box 4)
      - Project committee (Box 4)
      - Check list (Box 4)
      - Installation photographs (Box 4)
    - "Contemporary Brazilian Prints,", May 5-25, 1958 (Box 4)
    - "Theatrical Posters of the Gay Nineties" (Library of Congress, Prints & Photographs Division), May 5-25, 1958 (Box 4)
  - 1958-1959
    - Schedule (Box 4)
    - Undergraduate Library exhibitions, 1958-1959 (Box 4)
    - "Contemporary Prints from Great Britain,", July 1958 (Box 4)
      (Oregon State College)
    - Religious Art-General Information, Summer 1958 (Box 4)
      (part of the "Religion in Contemporary Society" summer session)
    - "Sculpture Midwest 1957,", June 15-September 2, 1958 (Box 4)
      (Kalamazoo Institute of Arts)
    - "The Life of Christ (Prints from the Rosenwald Collection),", June 30-August 10, 1958 (Box 4)
    - "Jewish Mosaics (From Adam Through the Prophets),", July 1-August 10, 1958 (Box 4)
      (Jewish Educational Committee of New York)
    - "Immaculate Heart College (Mosaics),", July 1-August 10, 1958 (Box 4)
    - "Morris Kantor Paintings and Drawings,", Summer 1958 (Box 4)
    - "The New Landscape in Art and Science,", October 1-26, 1958 (Box 4)
    - "Art Department Faculty,", October 16-November 23, 1958 (Box 4)
    - "Eleventh National Print Exhibition" (The Brooklyn Museum), November 1-30, 1958 (Box 4)
    - "Prints for Christmas,", November 25-December 15, 1958 (Box 4)
    - "Prints and Drawings in Honor of Jean Paul Slusser,", December 7-31, 1958 (Box 4)
    - "Modern Sculptures and Sculptors' Drawings from the Permanent Collection,", December 1958-January 1959 (Box 4)
    - "Permanent Collections-Contemporary Paintings," December 23, 1958-? (Box 4)
    - "Rackham Grant Exhibitions (Richard Wilt, Richard Sears, Albert P. Mullen),", January 7-March 31, 1959 (Box 4)
    - "Cesnola and Havenmeyer Collections," January 7-February 1, February 5-March 3, 1959 (Box 4)
    - "Footlights and Skylights: Theatrical Photographs of the American Stage, 1860-1900," February 1-28, 1959 and "The Direct Approach: Edward Weston, Ansel Adams, Brett Weston and Pirkle Jones," May 1959 (Box 4)
    - "Master Drawings and Prints from the Permanent Collection,", February 4-March 1, 1959 (Box 4)
      (includes label)
    - "Fourteen Rotterdam Artists,", March 1-25, 1959 (Box 4)
      (Netherlands Information Service, Holland, Michigan)
    - "The American Line: Drawings by American Artists, 1850-1950" (Addison Gallery of American Art), March 1-21, 1959 (Box 4)
    - "Mackenzie Show" (Alix and Warren Mackenzie: Potters), March 1959 (Box 4)
    - "Original Book Illustrations,", April 1959 (Box 4)
    - "Print Symposium" (Gabor Peterdi, Garo Antreasian, Rudy Pozzatti), April 7-20, 1959 (Box 4)
    - "Persian Art Before and After the Mongol Conquest,", April 8-May 17, 1959 (Box 4)
    - "Selections from The Edward Root Collection" (Munson-Williams-Proctor Institute), April 22-June 14, 1959 (Box 4)
      (20th century American paintings)
    - "Mrs. Wilt's Children's Class,", May 13-June 13, 1959 (Box 4)
      (Children's Creative Activities Program: Ann Arbor Recreation Department and Dramatic Arts Center)
    - "Michigan Water Color Society,", June 1959 (Box 4)
  - 1959-1960
    - Schedule (Box 4)
    - Undergraduate Library exhibitions [UGLI], 1959-1960
      - Schedule (Box 4)
      - "Prints-City and Country Views-Museum Collection,", June 10-September 30, 1959 (Box 4)
      - "Contemporary Japanese Pottery and the Traditions of Chinese Pottery,", June 22-August 9, 1959 (Box 4)
        (Asia Society)
      - "Landscape Design: Work of Dan Kiley,", November 5-25, 1959 (Box 4)
      - "Contemporary European Color Prints-Museum Collection,", December 7, 1959-February 24, 1960 (Box 4)
      - "The Figure (Prints)-Museum Collection,", February 25-April 25, 1960 (Box 4)
      - "The Private World of Pablo Picasso,", May 1-22, 1960 (Box 4)
    - Alumni Memorial Hall exhibitions [AMH], 1959-1960
      - "Young British Painters,", June 16-August 9, 1959 (Box 4)
      - "The City in Transition: Detroit Plans Its Future,", June 29-August 9, 1959 (Box 4)
        (Detroit Planning Commission)
        (part of the "Modern Man Looks Forward" summer session)
      - "Eskimo Art of the Canadian Eastern Arctic,", September 15-October 11, 1959 (Box 4)
        (Eskimo Art, Inc.)
      - "Japanese Prints-Museum Collection,", October 4-November 1, 1959 (Box 4)
      - "Fulbright Painters,", October 21-November 15, 1959 (Box 4)
      - "[Mountain of God:] Mount Sinai and the Monastery of St. Catherine" (Princeton University Library), November 14-December 22, 1959 (Box 4)
      - "Prints for Christmas,", November 18-December 13, 1959 (Box 4)
        (Ferdinand Roten)
      - "Painting in Post-War Italy: 1945-1957,", December 5-27, 1959 (Box 4)
      - "Rackham Grant Exhibitions (Louis Tavelli, Frank Cassara, Fred Vidar),", January 6-April 6, 1960 (Box 4)
      - "Architecture in Venezuela,", January 12-30, 1960 (Box 4)
        (Venezuelan Society of Architects and Creole Petroleum Corporation)
      - "Gandhara Sculpture from Pakistan Museums,", February 21-March 13, 1960 (Box 4)
      - "Prints from Michigan Collections. Part I: 15th, 16th and 17th Centuries,", March 6-27, 1960 (Box 4)
      - "Abraham Rattner Retrospective Exhibition,", March 13-April 6, 1960 (Box 4)
      - "Clay Forms,", April 13-May 15, 1960 (Box 4)
      - "Images at Mid-Century,", April 13-June 12, 1960 (Box 4)
        (James Johnson Sweeney)
      - "Art and the Found Object,", April 16-May 1, 1960 (Box 4)
      - North Gallery [Drawing, Graphic processes, Oil painting], April-June 1960 (Box 4)
      - "Five Centuries of Drawing" (The Cooper Union Museum), May 15-June 5, 1960 (Box 4)
  - 1960-1961
    - Undergraduate Library exhibitions [UGLI], 1960-1961
      - Schedule (Box 4)
      - "American Figure Drawing,", June 10-August 8, 1960 (Box 4)
        (Corcoran Gallery of Art and UMMA)
      - "American Drawings-Museum Collection,", October 24-November 14, 1960 (Box 4)
      - "Lithographs of Fantin-Latour,", November 15-December 18, 1960 (Box 4)
      - "Contemporary Drawings and Prints-Museum Collection,", December 18, 1960-January 1961 (Box 4)
      - "Prints and Drawings by Jacques Villon" (Boston Public Library), February 1-28, 1961 (Box 4)
      - "Whistler Prints-Museum Collection,", March 1961 (Box 4)
      - "The Photograph as Poetry" (Pasadena Art Museum), April 8-May 7, 1961 (Box 4)
        (Western Association of Art Museums)
      - "Contemporary European Prints,", May 8-June 26, 1961 (Box 4)
    - Alumni Memorial Hall exhibitions [AMH], 1960-1961
      - Schedule (Box 4)
      - "German Artists of Today,", June 27-August 7, 1960 (Box 4)
      - "Piranesi" (Etchings by Giovanni Battista Piranesi), September 18-October 18, 1960 (Box 4)
      - "The Artist in His Studio" (photographs by Alexander Liberman), October 8-30, 1960 (Box 4)
      - "Small Sculpture,", October 23-November 13, 1960 (Box 4)
        (Bertha Shaefer Gallery)
      - "Rembrandt Prints,", October 23-November 20, 1960 (Box 4)
      - "Contemporary Color Prints,", November 4-23, 1960 (Box 4)
        (Nils Lou, for History of Art course)
      - "Prints for Christmas,", November 16-December 7, 1960 (Box 4)
      - "Rackham Grant Exhibitions (Irving Kaufman, Emil Weddige),", November 20-December 21, 1960 (Box 4)
      - "16 Old Master Drawings-Museum of Art Collections,", November 23, 1960-February 12, 1961 (Box 4)
      - "Contemporary Paintings-Museum of Art Collections,", December 1960-February 12, 1961 (Box 4)
      - "Contemporary Drawings and Watercolors-Museum of Art Collections,", December 1960-February 1961 (Box 4)
      - "Rackham Grant Exhibitions (Milton Cohen, Albert Weber),", January 11-February 12, 1961 (Box 4)
      - "Rackham Grant Exhibitions (Leonard Zamiska),", February 15-March 19, 1961 (Box 4)
      - "Prints from Michigan Collections. Part II: 18th and First Half of 19th Centuries,", February 19-March 19, 1961 (Box 4)
      - "Americans-A View from the East" (Japanese prints from the Boehringer Collection), March 1-31, 1961 (Box 4)
      - "Children's Creative Arts Classes,", April 3-May 14, 1961 (Box 4)
        (Ann Arbor Recreation Department)
      - "The Face of the Fifties,", April 12-May 28, 1961 (Box 4)
        (Whitney Museum of American Art)
      - "Print Exhibition (Romas Viesulas, Dean Jackson Meeker, Lee Chesney),", May 14-June 4, 1961 (Box 4)
      - Rackham Grant Exhibitions-Copy, [January-March 1961] (Box 4)
  - 1961-1962
    - Schedule (Box 5)
    - "Michigan and the Civil War,", June 28-August 13, 1961 (Box 5)
      (part of the "Civil War" summer session)
    - "Creative Engineering: The Work of Pier Luigi Nervi" [UGLI], June 28-August 27, 1961 (Box 5)
    - "Contemporary French Posters,", July 12-29, 1961 (Box 5)
      (Alliance Franáaise, The Ann Arbor Chapter)
    - "Contemporary German Prints,", July 19-September 3, 1961 (Box 5)
    - "Paintings for Purchase Consideration,", September 15-October 11, 1961 (Box 5)
    - "Latin America: New Departures,", October 15-November 12, 1961 (Box 5)
      (Institute of Contemporary Art)
    - "Bay Printmakers' Society Sixth National Exhibition" [UGLI], October 15-November 14, 1961 (Box 5)
    - "Rackham Grant Exhibitions I (Thomas F. McClure, Richard Wilt, Chet H. LaMore),", November 15-December 10, 1961 (Box 5)
    - "Prints for Christmas,", November 15-December 10, 1961 (Box 5)
    - "America in Daguerreotypes" [UGLI], January 1962 (Box 5)
    - "Faculty Exhibition: Department of Art, Ohio State University,", January 10-28, 1962 (Box 5)
      (Ohio State University)
    - "Rackham Grant Exhibitions II (John L. Goodyear, Richard H. Jennings),", January 10-February 4, 1962 (Box 5)
    - "Chinese Art at Michigan,", January 19-February 4, 1962 (Box 5)
    - "Great Book Illustrations of the 15th and 16th Centuries" [UGLI], February 1962 (Box 5)
      (Ferdinand Roten Galleries)
    - "The Technique of Fresco Painting,", February 3-25, 1962 (Box 5)
    - "Rackham Grant Exhibitions III (Paul R. Suttman, William A. Lewis, Albert P. Mullen),", February 14-March 18, 1962 (Box 5)
    - "Tibetan Thang-Kas,", February 21-April 1, 1962 (Box 5)
      (Museum of Anthropology and Detroit Institute of Art)
    - "Sculpture and Sculptors' Drawings for Purchase Consideration,", March 4-25, 1962 (Box 5)
    - "The Heart of India" [UGLI], March 7-28, 1962 (Box 5)
    - "The Art of Jens Jensen: Landscape Architect,", April 18-May 14, 1962 (Box 5)
      (College of Architecture and Design)
    - "A Generation of Draughtsmen,", April 25-May 29, 1962 (Box 5)
    - "Mies Van Der Rohe" [UGLI], May 8-30, 1962 (Box 5)
    - "Contemporary Prints from Japan,", June 23-August 25, 1962 (Box 5)
    - "The Architecture of Alden B. Dow,", June 14-August 12, 1962 (Box 5)
      (Alden Dow and Alumni Association)
  - 1962-1963
    - Schedule (Box 5)
    - Undergraduate Library exhibitions [UGLI], 1962-1963
      - Selections from the Museum of Art Collections ("Contemporary Color Prints," September 12-October 24, 1962 "19th Century French Prints," April 2-24, 1963), 1962-1963 (Box 5)
      - "Roads,", October 28-November 18, 1962 (Box 5)
      - "Color Photography by Howard Dearstyne,", November 21-December 19, 1962 (Box 5)
        (Bloomfield Art Association)
      - "Prints by Post-Impressionists" (National Gallery of Art), January 6-27, 1963 (Box 5)
      - "The Face of Poetry,", February 15-March 6, 1963 (Box 5)
      - "Preservation: The Heritage of Progress" (National Trust for Historic Preservation), March 8-29, 1963 (Box 5)
      - "Vis-a-Vis: Photographs and Prints from the Metropolitan Museum of Art,", April 26-May 17, 1963 (Box 5)
    - Alumni Memorial Hall exhibitions [AMH], 1962-1963
      - "18th and 19th Century Stage Designs from the May r-Fajt Collection,", June 29-August 12, 1962 (Box 5)
        (Helene C. Seiferheld Master Drawings)
      - "German Expressionists" (Beckmann, Ernst, Feininger, Grosz), October 18-November 25, 1962 (Box 5)
        (UMMA and Detroit Institute of Arts
      - "Contemporary American Painting: Selections from the Neuberger Collection,", October 21-November 18, 1962 (Box 5)
      - "Art Nouveau Graphics,", November 7-December 5, 1962 (Box 5)
      - "Chi-Kwan Chen: A Decade in Retrospect" (Mi Chou Gallery), November 28-December 16, 1962 (Box 5)
      - "Islamic Art,", November 16-April 28, 1962 (Box 5)
      - "Art Nouveau Sampler,", December 15, 1962-January 20, 1963 (Box 5)
      - "Contemporary Watercolors and Drawings for Purchase Consideration,", January 13-February 10, 1963 (Box 5)
      - "Michigan State University Print Exhibition,", February 3-24, 1963 (Box 5)
      - "The Ideal Theater: Eight Concepts,", February 21-April 2, 1963 (Box 5)
      - "Marcel Breuer: Architect,", March 1-17, 1963 (Box 5)
        (includes printed transcription of artist's lecture)
      - "Classical Art" (in connection with Marvin Eisenberg's Classical Studies 101 class), March 15-April 21, 1963 (Box 5)
      - "Medieval Art" (in connection with Marvin Eisenberg's Classical Studies 101 class), April 2-May 26, 1963 (Box 5)
      - "Contemporary European Painting for Purchase Consideration,", April 17-May 19, 1963 (Box 5)
  - 1963-1964
    - Schedule (Box 5)
    - Undergraduate Library exhibitions [UGLI], 1963-1964
      - "Contemporary American Landscape Architecture,", October 19-November 10, 1963 (Box 5)
      - "Japanese Prints,", November 15-December 9, 1963 (Box 5)
      - "Pratt Graphic Art Center Exhibition,", December 1963 (Box 5)
        (Traveling Art Guild)
      - "European Posters,", January 18-February 9, 1964 (Box 5)
      - "Ideas in Images: An Exhibition of 100 Photographs,", February 21-March 13, 1964 (Box 5)
      - "Photographs by Irving Penn,", March 16-April 6, 1964 (Box 5)
      - "Prints by Mary Cassatt,", April 10-30, 1964 (Box 5)
    - Alumni Memorial Hall exhibitions [AMH], 1963-1964
      - "Contemporary Water Colors from France,", June 20-August 20, 1963 (Box 5)
      - "Hogarth's 'A Rake's Progress',", September 8-October 20, 1963 (Box 5)
      - "Six Painters and the Object,", October 9-November 3, 1963 (Box 5)
        (Guggenheim Museum)